flywheelsports.com 2015-04-30

# Flywheel Sports Privacy Policy | Flywheel Sports

### Flywheel Sports Privacy Policy

#### Effective January 24, 2012

Flywheel Sports, Inc. ("Flywheel") understands the importance of privacy, and we want you to be as comfortable as possible visiting our website and using our services. This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use any of the features offered from time to time on our website, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in, and the terms of, this privacy policy. These practices may change, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a "going forward" basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only. If you link to other websites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

#### Collection of Information

We collect personally identifiable information such as names, postal addresses, email addresses, credit card information etc., when voluntarily submitted by users of (and visitors to) our website. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request, to improve the experience on the Flywheel site, to ensure a successful experience at a Flywheel studio, and to adhere to the Membership Terms and Conditions you agree when you make a purchase on our website. Flywheel may also log non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users of the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website’s services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to users. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. We may also record information about your usage, such as the time and frequency of your usage of the Flywheel website. If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your account. We may use clear GIFs (a.k.a. "Web Beacons") in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. We may also use your email address to send updates, newsletters or other news regarding Flywheel. Users may choose not to receive email of these types by following opt-out instructions contained in such emails or by changing their notification settings under the "My Account" section of the Flywheel website. Flywheel reserves the right to send you important notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.

#### Cookie/Tracking Technology

The Flywheel website may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the website, and understanding how visitors use the website. Cookies can also help customize our website for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

#### Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (i) permitted or required by law; (ii) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or (iii) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

#### Children Under Age 13

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please DO NOT attempt to register on our website or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on our website. In the event that we learn that any personal information has been submitted to the website from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as reasonably possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [privacy@flywheelsports.com](mailto:privacy@flywheelsports.com "privacy@flywheelsports.com").

#### Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18

If you are between the ages of 13 and 18, you may register on our website only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

#### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All marketing emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further marketing mailings.

We use industry-standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information (such as firewalls and secure sockets layer software) where appropriate. Nevertheless, absolute security does not yet exist on the internet.

As we continue to evolve our website and incorporate new technologies to improve communication, our policies may change. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis to stay abreast of our most current privacy policy practices.

Questions regarding this policy and our practice should be directed to the Flywheel Sports Customer Service department, by e-mail to [privacy@flywheelsports.com](mailto:privacy@flywheelsports.com "privacy@flywheelsports.com"), by telephone at [(212) 242-9433](tel:2129429433) or by postal mail to Flywheel Sports, PO Box 1816, New York, NY 10113
